airasiabig.com 2017-05-19

# 

                                          Privacy Policy
1.     GENERAL
   1.1   This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) is provided by Tune Money Sdn Bhd (“Tune Money”) and
         Think Big Digital Sdn Bhd (“TBD”) collectively with respect to the issuance of the prepaid
         products by Tune Money and operation and management of the AirAsia BIG Loyalty
         Programme by TBD, and the provision of services thereunder (collectively referred to as “we”,
         “our” and “us”).
   1.2   This Privacy Policy describes how and when we collect your personal information, what that
         information may be used for, who uses it, when it may be disclosed to other parties, how you
         can access your details and seek correction of your details, the control your own personal
         information and how you can contact us.
   1.3   By visiting www.airasiabig.com, you are deemed to have read and agreed to be bound by this
         Privacy Policy.
2.     NOTICE
   2.1   This Privacy Policy serves as a notice pursuant to the Malaysian Personal Data Protection Act
         2010.
   2.2   We may modify, vary or update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect any changes to
         our privacy practices. We will notify you of these changes to our Privacy Policy on our website
         www.airasiabig.com (“Website”). In any case, an updated version of this Privacy Policy is
         always available on our Website at all times. Please check our Website regularly for updates
         to our Privacy Policy.
3.     INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE
   3.1   We may collect and hold personal information/data (“Personal Information”) about you or
         someone else whom you have provided us with information of (“Third Party”), that is,
         information that can identify you or such Third Party, including without limitation, full name,
         postal and email address, other contact details, identification details, payment details, and
         any other information relevant to us in providing you with the services you and/or the Third
         Party are, or someone else you know, is seeking, which we receive from you through our
         Website, customer service centre, social media sites, walk-in or any distribution channels. You
         represent and warrant that you have obtained the consent of such Third Party or are
         otherwise entitled to provide us with their Personal Information and to view or change their
         information. You agree to indemnify us in the event we suffer any loss or damage as a result
         of your failure to comply with the same.
   3.2   You are responsible for ensuring that the Personal Information you provide us is accurate,
         complete and not misleading and that such Personal Information is kept up to date.
                                                                                               Page 1 of 5

3.3    We may collect Personal Information in one or more of the following circumstances or for one
       or more of the following purposes:
    (a)     to provide you with products and/or services which you have subscribed for and to
            notify you about important changes or developments to the features;
    (b)     to send you information on products and services, and special promotional offers,
            newsletters or customer survey forms and questionnaires;
    (c)     to provide you with information on any programs (e.g. loyalty programs, including but
            not limited to the AirAsia BIG Loyalty Programme) or transactions you have undertaken;
    (d)     to process your payment transactions and for other operational and administrative
            purposes, including without limitation, sending you notifications, and managing your
            account;
    (e)     updating and managing the accuracy of our records; prevention, detection or
            prosecution of crime, and complying with legal and regulatory obligations;
    (f)     assessment and analysis behaviour scoring, market, product and trend analysis and
            market research (if any);
    (g)     to conduct internal activities, administrative, operational, marketing, planning, product
            or service development, troubleshooting and research requirements;
    (h)     to administer your participation in contests or campaigns that we may run from time to
            time;
    (i)     to provide you with information on products and services of TBD and Tune Money and
            our related corporations, affiliates, subsidiaries and associates;
    (j)     to provide you with information on products and services of our business partners;
    (k)     cross selling, marketing and promotions including administering offers and
            competitions;
    (l)     communications and ensuring customer satisfaction, which may include conducting
            surveys to improve the quality of our products and services, responding to inquiries and
            complaints and to generally resolve disputes or to enforce our terms and conditions,
            including the terms and conditions relating to the products and/or services;
    (m)     maintaining your card account history for present and future reference (if any);
    (n)     enabling an actual or proposed assignee of TBD or Tune Money, or participant or sub-
            participant of TBD or Tune Money to evaluate your transactions which are intended to
            be the subject of the assignment, participation or sub-participation (if any);
    (o)     protecting TBD’s and Tune Money’s interests and other ancillary or related purposes;
    (p)     for such other purposes as set out in any other terms and conditions (including product
            terms and conditions) and campaign terms and conditions (if applicable); and
                                                                                            Page 2 of 5

       (q)      for any purpose made known to you at the time of collection of your personal
                information.
       (collectively referred to as “Purposes”)
   3.4   At any time you may opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us by contacting us
         (see the CONTACTING US section below) and we will ensure that your name is removed from
         our mailing list.
   3.5   We use general, aggregated information to generate statistics and measure site activity to
         improve the usefulness of customer visits. Such information does not include Personal
         Information.
   3.6   Please take note that if required for the foregoing Purposes, your Personal Information may
         be transferred to locations outside Malaysia.
   3.7   We may disclose your Personal Information to:
       (a)      our related corporations, affiliates, subsidiaries, associates, contractors, licensees,
                advisors, vendors, service providers, merchants, strategic partners, third party
                contractors, whether located within or outside Malaysia;
       (b)      payment network operators (including VISA, MasterCard, China Union Pay),
                governmental agencies, regulatory authorities (including Bank Negara Malaysia)
                whether located within or outside Malaysia
         for the Purpose.
         Your Personal Information may also be disclosed to other third parties with whom we have
         commercial relationships, for marketing, advertising and related purposes, unless you have
         indicated that you do not wish for us to disclose to such third parties for marketing and
         advertising purposes, and as required or authorised under law or provided in co-operation
         with any governmental authority.
   3.8   Please note that it is necessary for TBD and Tune Money to process your personal information
         for the Purpose, and without which TBD and Tune Money will not be able to provide the
         product and/or service that you have requested from TBD or Tune Money or to perform
         and/or carry out any of the abovementioned Purposes. If you fail to provide us with Personal
         Information stated in paragraph 3.1 above, we may not be able to perform and/or carry out
         any of the Purposes.
4.     MARKETING AND PROMOTIONAL COMMUNICATIONS
   4.1   We may use the Personal Information provided to send you information on products and
         services, and special or promotional offers, newsletters or customer survey forms and
         questionnaires unless you have indicated that you do not wish to receive such materials.
   4.2   You may opt out of receiving any communications from us at any time by clicking on the
         “unsubscribe link” on the relevant marketing communications or contact us with your request
         (see the CONTACTING US section below).
                                                                                              Page 3 of 5

5.     SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
   5.1   We will take reasonable steps to protect any Personal Information we receive from you via
         our Website from misuse and loss and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.
         We may hold your information in either electronic or hard copy form or retain third parties to
         hold that information on our behalf. Where required by applicable laws, Personal Information
         will be destroyed or de-identified when no longer needed.
   5.2   By providing us with Personal Information or using our services or our Website, you consent
         to the transfer, storage and processing of Personal Information to where our servers, central
         database and system facilities are located and/or operated, which may be outside your
         country of domicile or the location where you access our Website to provide Personal
         Information, and which may include, among others, Malaysia, Singapore, India, the United
         States and the United Kingdom.
   5.3   However as the Website is linked to the internet, and the internet is inherently insecure, we
         cannot provide any assurance regarding the security of transmission of information you
         communicate to us and you do so at your own risk.
6.     LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
   6.1   Our Website may contain links to websites operated by third parties (“Third Party Websites”).
         We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of Third Party Websites. Third
         Party Websites are responsible for informing you about their own privacy practices.
7.     ACCESS AND CORRECTION
   7.1   You may request access to any Personal Information we hold about you or any Third Party
         whose Personal Information you had provided at any time by contacting us (see the
         CONTACTING US section below). Where we hold information that you are entitled to access,
         we will endeavour to provide you with suitable means of accessing it (e.g. by emailing or
         mailing it to you).
   7.2   If you believe that Personal Information we hold about you is incorrect, incomplete or
         inaccurate, then you may amend the same yourself at the Website or request to amend it. We
         will consider if the information requires amendment. If we do not agree that there are grounds
         for amendment then we will add a note to the Personal Information stating that you disagree
         with it. You may also, at any time hereafter, request, in writing, to limit the processing of your
         Personal Information (including personal data of others provided by you).
   7.3   In accordance with the Malaysian Personal Data Protection Act 2010, and to the extent not
         limited by any other applicable law (if applicable), we may:
       (1)      charge a fee for processing your request for access or correction to the Personal
                Information; and
       (2)      refuse to comply with your request for correction to the Personal Information and give
                you a reason for our refusal.
                                                                                                  Page 4 of 5

8.     COOKIES
   8.1    We may use cookies in our Website to:-
       (1)      maintain your session and required details during the application, subscription,
                registration process and during transactions (session cookie);
       (2)      collect website usage data for statistical/analytics purposes (analytics cookie); and
       (3)      direct you to the correct landing page based on your geo-location (geo-targeting
                cookie).
   8.2    You may instruct your browser, by changing its setting, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt
          you before accepting a cookie from the websites that you visit. Our Website will not function
          properly if the cookie setting is disabled.
9.     CONTACTING US
   9.1    If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or any concerns or a complaint regarding
          the treatment of your privacy by us pursuant to the Malaysian Personal Data Protection Act
          2010, please contact us via registered mail or email (which must be sent from your email
          address that you registered with us) at:-
       Personal Data Protection Division
       Unit 19-05-01, Level 5
       Wisma Tune
       Lorong Dungun
       Damansara Heights
       50490 Kuala Lumpur
       Malaysia
       Email: pdpa.admin@airasiabig.com
10.    CONFLICT BETWEEN ENGLISH TEXT AND OTHER TRANSLATION
10.1   If there is any conflict or discrepancy between the English text of terms and conditions of this
       Privacy Policy and any translation thereof, the English text shall prevail and supersede any
       other translation or any other version in any other language.
                                                                                                 Page 5 of 5
